Super Tokimeki Propaganda Department in Indonesia!
That's a crime to say.
What are you doing? I'm serious.
I'm invisible.
They're disappearing.
He's gone. He's gone.
Yes!
Ah!
Aah! We're moving!
We're moving!
OK, OK!
OK!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Smile green fur spurs
Aah! Aah! Aah!
I got it! I got it! Yes! I got it!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Whoo!
Whoo! Isn't that nice?
It's good, right?
Oh, man!
Wow!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Whoo!
Ha-ha-ha!
Whoa!
Uh-oh.
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh no!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Chocolate mania
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Uhh!
Whoo!
Wah!
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, no!
Oh no!
Oh, man!
You're so cute! Turn around!
Oh! Cute!
You're cute!
You're Japanese!
Yay! Japanese!
Thank you!
See you later!
Cute!
Hot
Hot.
Me too.
Hello.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
I love, love, love.
Can I come in?
He's so cute.
She's cute.
You look good.
Oh, my gosh.
Look at that.
Cute.
Sunglasses.
The wind is amazing.
Haay!
Ta-omen
Ore Ore Ore
Cute.
Cute!
Here she comes.
What did you say?
Kasukumpa!
So cute.
Gotcha!
Ghetto!
So cute!
I want to eat it!
I want to eat.
Good night, Mr. Okun.
Good night, boy.
Good night, Okun.
Embarrassing
Beautiful.
I like it.
When did you do it?
Menga.
You're beautiful.
We just kissed.
It's so biotic.
This is hard.
You're going to get very wet.
It's not wet.
You're ducking.
It's beautiful.
Yakkie.
He's so cute!
Yay! Yay!
Movie! Movie!
Cute! Cute!
Oh! Cute!
Aah! Oh, my God! Cute!
Aah! So cute! So cute!
So cute! So cute!
Yeah!
You know what's popular right now?
Oh, there it is!
Oh, here it comes!
Oh, wow. Oh, wow.
You're so cute.
Bye bye!
Thank you!
Bye bye! See you later!
Let's go!
He's so cute.
Oshimimi
Three.
Two.
reaction
cute
Hee hee hee ow!
Foo
You're hot.
I beg you.
Oh-kun, he's eating a toy for an extra treat.
Oh-kun is eating a toy.
ookun eating toy
Ookun is eating his toy.
Why do you have to go to bed today before you go to sleep?
Why don't you kiss daddy?
I don't know anymore.
Why did you get so mad at me for not talking?
I'm not even dizzy. When I was in love...
You know what? I love you.
Sometimes, sometimes, it bothers you.
Don't be afraid to accept it.
Oh!
Cute, cute, cute, I love you.
I can't stop loving you.
I'm so sweet, I'm so sweet, I'm so sweet, I'm so sweet, I love you so much
I've got you all to myself.
Välkku baekku.
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday.
After the rain, the cityscape turns color.
I'll paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my broken heart.
blotting out the future.
Subtitle: Kyou
I can tell you now
Whenever you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
So that I can smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good-bye Goodbye, Yesterday's Me
After the rain, the streets sparkle
My heart is fine as I've grown accustomed to it, rainbow pools, make a rainbow sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye, I was there yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering.
Maru ga hokoro wa hana katachi wa hana katachi wa hana katachi wa hana katachi wa hana
I'm going to wear a rainbow dress
LaLaLa...
Please subscribe to our channel!